module.exports = [
  {
    q_id: 1,
    a: "Mikel Arteta",

    b: "Chris Wilder",

    c: "Frank Lampard",

    d: "Jurgen Klopp",

    q_prompt:
      "Who was the first Premier League manager or player to test positive for coronavirus?",

    q_correctAnswer: "a",
  },

  {
    q_id: 2,
    a: "Manuel Pellegrini",

    b: "Nigel Pearson",

    c: "Eddie Howe",

    d: "Chris Wilder",

    q_prompt: "Who was the first Premier League manager to be sacked in 2020?",

    q_correctAnswer: "b",
  },

  {
    q_id: 3,
    a: "Quique Setien",

    b: "Xavi Hernandez",

    c: "Ernesto Valverde",

    d: "Rai Garcia",

    q_prompt: "Who preceded Ronald Koeman as Barcelona manager?",

    q_correctAnswer: "a",
  },

  {
    q_id: 4,
    a: "2-1 loss to Newcastle United",

    b: "1-1 drew vs Manchester City",

    c: "1-1 drew vs Fulham",

    d: "5-1 loss to Crystal Palace",

    q_prompt:
      "Slaven Bilic's last game for West Brom before he was sacked ended with which scoreline?",

    q_correctAnswer: "b",
  },
  {
    q_id: 5,
    a: "Stuttgart",

    b: "Werder Bremen",

    c: "Schalke",

    d: "Borussia Dortmund",

    q_prompt:
      "Which Bundesliga side has already sacked two managers this season?",

    q_correctAnswer: "c",
  },
  {
    q_id: 6,
    a: "Vitesse",

    b: "AZ Alkmaar",

    c: "ADO Den Haag",

    d: "Ajax",

    q_prompt:
      "Alan Pardew left which Dutch side by 'mutual consent' back in April 2020?",

    q_correctAnswer: "c",
  },
  {
    q_id: 7,
    a: "Timo Werner",

    b: "Thomas Partey",

    c: "Kai Havertz",

    d: "Amad Diallo",

    q_prompt:
      "Which player was the most expensive Premier League import in the summer of 2020?",

    q_correctAnswer: "c",
  },
  {
    q_id: 8,
    a: "Real Sociedad",

    b: "Villarreal",

    c: "Sevilla",

    d: "Real Betis",

    q_prompt:
      "Valencia sold captain Dani Parejo and Francis Coquelin to which LaLiga side for a combined €8m?",

    q_correctAnswer: "b",
  },
  {
    q_id: 9,
    a: "Federico Chiesa",

    b: "Weston Mckennie",

    c: "Alvaro Morata",

    d: "Dejan Kulusevski",

    q_prompt: "Who was Andrea Pirlo's first signing as Juventus manager?",

    q_correctAnswer: "b",
  },
  {
    q_id: 10,
    a: "£35.8m",

    b: "£10m",

    c: "Nothing, he was a free transfer",

    d: "£27.3m",

    q_prompt: "How much did Liverpool pay Bayern Munich for Thiago?",

    q_correctAnswer: "d",
  },
  {
    q_id: 11,
    a: "Barcelona",

    b: "Benfica",

    c: "Ajax",

    d: "Standard Liege",

    q_prompt:
      "Jan Vertonghen left Tottenham after eight years to join which club on a free transfer?",

    q_correctAnswer: "b",
  },
  {
    q_id: 12,
    a: "Lisbon",

    b: "Madrid",

    c: "Turin",

    d: "Paris",

    q_prompt:
      "Which city hosted the final stages of the Champions League in August?",

    q_correctAnswer: "a",
  },
  {
    q_id: 13,
    a: "Tottenham",

    b: "RB Liepzig",

    c: "Real Madrid",

    d: "Lyon",

    q_prompt:
      "Which team knocked out Manchester City in the quarter-finals of the Champions League?",

    q_correctAnswer: "d",
  },
  {
    q_id: 14,
    a: "Kylian Mbappe",

    b: "Neymar",

    c: "Eric Maxim Choupo-Moting",

    d: "Thila Kehrer",

    q_prompt:
      "Who scored PSG's last minute winner against Atalanta in the quarter-finals?",

    q_correctAnswer: "c",
  },
  {
    q_id: 15,
    a: "Robert Lewandowski",

    b: "Alphonse Davies",

    c: "Thomas Muller",

    d: "Leroy Sane",

    q_prompt:
      "Who was awarded the Man of the Match award in Bayern's 8-2 thrashing of Barcelona?",

    q_correctAnswer: "c",
  },
  {
    q_id: 16,
    a: "Joshua Kimmich",

    b: "Kingsley Coman",

    c: "Leon Goretzka",

    d: "Robert Lewandowski",

    q_prompt:
      "Which Bayern Munich player scored the only goal of the Champions League final?",

    q_correctAnswer: "b",
  },
  {
    q_id: 17,
    a: "Mykonos",

    b: "Malia",

    c: "Santorini",

    d: "Crete",

    q_prompt:
      "Harry Maguire was arrested while on holiday on which Greek island?",

    q_correctAnswer: "a",
  },
  {
    q_id: 18,
    a: "Dominic Raab",

    b: "Priti Patel",

    c: "Matt Hancock",

    d: "Boris Johnson",

    q_prompt:
      "Which government minister accidentally called Marcus Rashford, 'Daniel Rashford' live on Sky News?",

    q_correctAnswer: "c",
  },
  {
    q_id: 19,
    a: "Paul Pogba",

    b: "Michail Antonio",

    c: "Patrick van Aanholt",

    d: "Jesse Lingard",

    q_prompt:
      "Which Premier League footballer had a Twitter spat with Katie Hopkins?",

    q_correctAnswer: "c",
  },
  {
    q_id: 20,
    a: "25",

    b: "5",

    c: "55",

    d: "32",

    q_prompt: "How many members of staff did Arsenal make redundant in August?",

    q_correctAnswer: "c",
  },
];
